militarybyowner.com 2014-11-30

# Privacy Policy

**MILITARYBYOWNER.COM PRIVACY POLICY**  
Effective Date: November 28, 2005

MilitaryByOwner.com is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our clients and visitors to the MilitaryByOwner.com web site. We are committed to keep your personal information secure. We have put this privacy policy in place so our clients know we consider this an important issue. This privacy policy will be updated from time to time so please check frequently for any changes. BY USING THIS WEB SITE YOU CONSENT TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY. 

  1. **MILITARYBYOWNER.COM DOES NOT SELL, RENT OR TRANSFER PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
MilitaryByOwner.com DOES NOT sell, rent or transfer to third parties, any of the personal information our clients give to us. We will not disclose your personal information to third parties without your consent. The information our clients give us is used to present their advertisement on the website based on their advertising request. Contact information that is not presented on the web site is used to stay in contact with the customer for billing purpose and follow-up. Our clients have the option of opting-in or out of our electronic newsletter. E-mail addresses of those opting-in are used to send that electronic newsletter to clients who have opted-in.

Advertisers are able to access their account at any time to change their Personal information such as address, phone number, email address, etc.

  2. **DISCLAIMER FOR DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
MILITARYBYOWNER.COM MAY DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IF REQUIRED BY LAW OR IN A GOOD FAITH BELIEF THAT DISCLOSURE OF THE INFORMATION IS NECESSARY TO RESOLVE A DISPUTE, ENFORCE THE TERMS OF USE AGREEMENT, RESPOND TO A USERS REQUEST FOR SERVICE OR PROTECT THE RIGHTS, PROPERTY AND PERSONNEL OF MILITARYBYOWNER.COM, IT’S USERS AND THE PUBLIC.**

  3. **STORAGE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
Personal information collected from clients is kept for five years from the last submitted ad. Clients have the option to reactivate past ads such as rental advertisers looking for new tenants. If you want your information purged before five years contact MilitaryByOwner.com in writing to request the information be purged before that time.

  4. **SECURITY**  
MilitaryByOwner.com has taken commercially reasonable measures to protect our client’s personal information from being stolen, lost, misused, transferred or misappropriated. Our client’s personal information is stored on a secure server and the data is verified secure by a third party who uses the strongest possible encryption. The database is password protected, with physical and server based security.

  5. **ADVERTISING BY THIRD PARTIES ON THE SITE/LIMITS ON LIABILITY.**  
MilitaryByOwner.com does have third party advertisers on the site. Many of those advertisers have a direct link to their site. Should a user decide to use the link to their site, MilitaryByOwner.com is not responsible for any information the third party advertiser might collect. By linking to their site you will be submitting to their Terms of Use and privacy policy. **WE LIMIT OUR LIABILITY ONLY TO THE INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT ON OUR SITE.**

  6. **OUTSIDE LINKS/LIMITS ON LIABILITY**  
Some of our advertisers provide links to other web sites. Other sites may collect data and personal information about you. Any information you submit to third parties is out of our control and we **LIMIT OUR LIABILITY ONLY TO THE INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT ON OUR SITE. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU MAY GIVE TO ONE OF OUR BUSINESS ADVERTISERS OR THEIR AFFILIATES.**

  7. **TELL US IF YOU THINK YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS HAVE BEEN VIOLATED.**  
If you think your privacy rights have been violated when using this web site, contact MilitaryByOwner.com via email and immediately report when and how the alleged violation occurred. We will do our best to determine the problem and respond to your concerns.
